<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>DeCore 1.0</name>
  <author>Daniledman</author>
  <url>http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=946228883</url>
  	<targetVersion>1.0.2055</targetVersion>
  <description>
DeCore brings in a lot of changes in game mechanics, so the player have to think differently and use new colony development strategy.
The mod makes the game significantly more comfortable to play and some of its aspects - more logical. The mod changes resources, apparel and production.
The majority of changes were made using patches, so the chance of incompatibility with other mods is very low.
This mod is the pack of small enhancements and adjustments that make the game better. Most of them were made by me; some were taken from other mods.
DeCore may become an indispensable part of the game for someone. Perhaps, it will serve as base for many modpacks. Will see)

If you want to remove the reception of hay from grass and tall grass, delete this file:
YOURSTEAM \ steamapps \ workshop \ content \ 294100 \ 951016023 \ Patches \ Prod14grassDELETE.xml"

List of changes (briefly):

Production recipes changes.
Floors rebalance
Production tables resource cost changes.
Buildings changes
Smart colonists.
Resource rebalance.
Skills rework
More resources from mechanoid disassembly
More growables
Selling animals
Smaller paste dispenser
The ability to remove the geyser using the developer mode
Hydroponics basin 1x5, , improved hydroponics textures
Hidden power conduit


Mod is compatible with your old saves and don't require new game.
Special thanks: Hrosts

________________________________________
DeCore вносит множество изменений в механику игры, побуждая игрока думать иначе и использовать новую стратегию развития колонии.
Мод делает игру значительно удобнее, а некоторые ее аспекты логичнее. Мод изменяет ресурсы, постройки, одежду, производство.
Большинство изменений создано с помощью патчей, а значит, вероятность конфликта с другими модами крайне мала.
Этот мод является сборником мелких поправок, значительно улучшающих игру, большую часть которых я придумал сам, некоторые заимствовал из других модов.
Для кого-то DeCore станет незаменимым, возможно он будет важной составной частью каждой сборки модов. Посмотрим))

Список изменений (кратко):

Изменение рецептов производства.
Ребаланс покрытий. 
Изменение затрат ресурсов на станки.
Изменение свойств построек.
Умные колонисты
Ребаланс ресурсов
Переработка навыков
Больше ресурсов при разборе механоидов
Больше посадок
Продажа животных
Уменьшенный дозатор пасты
Возможность удаления гейзера с использованием режима разработчика
Добавлена гидропоника 1х5, улучшены текстуры гидропоники
Добавлен скрытый кабель

Мод совместим со старыми сохранениями и не требует новой игры..
Бгагодарности: Hrosts


  </description>
</ModMetaData>